Edwin Way Teale Papers 1981.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series IV: Print Material, undated, 1885-1995
  - Subseries A: Containing EWT's writing, photos or about EWT, undated, 1894-1995
    - Magazines
      - Audubon. Edwin Way Teale & Samuel H. Gottsho "Springtime at Trail Wood", 67:3, 1965 May/June (Box 181:, Folder 3598)
      - Audubon. "Wondrous Birds and a Wondrous Lady", 67:4, 1965 July/August (Box 181:, Folder 3599)
      - Audubon. "In the Valley of Ice Age Wildlife", 67:5, 1965 September/October (Box 181:, Folder 3600)
      - Audubon. "The Selborne Nightingale", 72:5, 1970 September (Box 181:, Folder 3601)
      - Audubon. "Big Thicket- Crossroads of Nature", 73:3, 1971 May (Box 181:, Folder 3602)
      - Audubon. "Glaze Storm", 74:1, 1972 January (Box 181:, Folder 3603)
      - Audubon. Zwinger, Ann "The Day Before Spring", 74:3, 1972 May (Box 181:, Folder 3604)
      - Audubon. "Birds of an Old Farm", 76:3, 1974 May (Box 182:, Folder 3605)
      - Audubon. "Windows on Wildlife", 76:6, 1974 November (Box 182:, Folder 3606)
      - Audubon. Zwinger, Ann "Every Valley...", 78:2, 1976 March (Box 182:, Folder 3607)
      - Audubon. Zwinger, Ann "The Eagle's Fate...", 79:4, 1977 July (Box 182:, Folder 3608)
      - Audubon. "A Walk Through October", 80:5, 1978 September (Box 182:, Folder 3609)
      - Audubon. "Stems Beyond Counting, Flowers Unnumbered", 84:4, 1982 July (Box 182:, Folder 3610)
      - Audubon. Unknown article, 85:1, 1983 January (Box 182:, Folder 3611)
      - Audubon. "Children of the Sun" (writings by EWT), 84:4, 1987 July (Box 182:, Folder 3612)
      - Audubon. "ETCETERA" (mentions EWT), 93:3, 1991 May (Box 182:, Folder 3613)
      - Aviation. Welch, Bill "Long Only A Dream", 8:7, 1984 July (Box 182:, Folder 3613A)
      - BBC Television for Schools. "Exploring Your World", 1966 Spring (Box 183:, Folder 3614)
      - BBC Radio for Schools. "Science At Work: Animal Behavior", 1966 Spring (Box 183:, Folder 3615)
      - Beekeeping. Phillips, E. F. Boy Scouts Merit Badge Series, 1944 (Box 183:, Folder 3616)
      - Book Parade-BMI. "North With the Spring", 1956 (Box 183:, Folder 3617)
      - Bulletin of the Brooklyn Entomological Society. (reprint) "Collecting With A Camera", 35:4, 1940 October (Box 183:, Folder 3618)
      - Bulletin of the Brooklyn Entomological Society. (reprint) "George P. Engelhardt", 37:4, 1942 December (Box 183:, Folder 3619)
      - Camera. Photos of Polyphemus moth by EWT, 66:6, 1944 June (Box 183:, Folder 3620)
      - Canadian Audubon. "House of Bubbles", 22:1, 1960 January/February (Box 183:, Folder 3621)
      - Canadian Audubon. "The Incredible Ant", 21:2, 1959 March/April (Box 183:, Folder 3622)
      - Canadian Nature. "Wasps: A Life Story" Cover is missing, undated (Box 183:, Folder 3623)
      - Canadian Nature. "North America's Largest Moth", 6:2, 1944 March/April (Box 183:, Folder 3624)
      - Collier's. "Superbug" (article only), 1944 March 11 (Box 183:, Folder 3625)
      - Compressed Air. Skerrett, R.G. "A Modern Noah's Ark", 50:7, 1945 July (Box 183:, Folder 3626)
      - Connecticut Audubon. Cover & "Visitors' Guide to Trail Wood", 7:1, 1986 Winter (Box 183:, Folder 3626A)
      - Connecticut Audubon. Farrand, John Jr. "Trail Wood", 1989 Winter (Box 183:, Folder 3626B)
      - The Conservationist. Davis, Millard C. "Widened Horizons for the Dune Boy", 28:5, 1974 April/May (Box 183:, Folder 3627)
      - The Conservationist. Santora, Pat "Edwin Way Teale-A Man Aware", 36:4, 1982 January/February (Box 183:, Folder 3628)
      - The Conservationist. Faust, J.L. Letter "Edwin Way Teale", 36:6, 1982 May/June (Box 183:, Folder 3629)
      - Coronet. "They Carve Their Careers Out of Nature", 20:1, 1946 May (Box 183:, Folder 3630)
      - Coronet. "The Incredible Ant", 26:2, 1949 June (Box 183:, Folder 3631)
      - Coronet. "Kingdom of the Night", 27:1, 1949 November (Box 183:, Folder 3632)
      - Coronet. "Nature's Cathedral", 27:3, 1950 January (Box 184:, Folder 3633)
      - Coronet. "Fabre: the Explorer Who Stayed Home", 29:4, 1951 February (Box 184:, Folder 3634)
      - Coronet. "The Praying Mantis: Friend of Man", 30:3, 1951 July (Box 184:, Folder 3635)
      - Coronet. "The Most Amazing Insect", 30:5, 1951 September (Box 184:, Folder 3636)
      - Coronet. "How Do They Move?", 36:5, 1954 September (Box 184:, Folder 3637)
      - Coronet. "The Whooping Crane's Wonderful Comeback", 49:1, 1960 November (Box 184:, Folder 3638)
      - Cue. (Film Listing for one of EWT's films), 1948 August 28 (Box 184:, Folder 3639)
      - Current Biography. (Bio. Of EWT), 22:11, 1961 December (Box 184:, Folder 3640)
      - Defenders. Santora, Pat "Teale's Natural Legacy", 56:5, 1981 October (Box 184:, Folder 3641)
      - Delaware Today. Volkman, Arthur G. "Covers, Blocks, Posts and Scrapers", 1969 December (Box 184:, Folder 3642)
      - Denver Quarterly. Wilson, David S. "Natural Nature", proof of article- about EWT, 4:2, 1969 Summer (Box 184:, Folder 3643)
      - Du und das Tier. "Winziges Wunderwerk Inseckten" (article only), 1959 March (Box 184:, Folder 3644)
      - The Earlhamite. 1:1-18, Volume of bulletins, 1894-1895 (Box 184:, Folder 3645)
      - The Earlhamite. 55:2, 55:4, 1934 January, July (Box 184:, Folder 3646)
      - The Earlhamite., 1948 Fall (Box 184:, Folder 3647)
      - The Earlhamite., 1953 Spring (Box 184:, Folder 3648)
      - The Earlhamite. 76:3, 1955 Fall (Box 184:, Folder 3649)
      - The Earlhamite., 1958 April (Box 184:, Folder 3650)
      - The Earlhamite., 1958 July (Box 184:, Folder 3651)
      - The Earlhamite. 84:2, 1963 April (Box 184:, Folder 3652)
      - The Earlhamite. 87:2, 1966 April (Box 184:, Folder 3653)
      - The Earlhamite. 94:1, 1973 Winter (Box 184:, Folder 3654)
      - Earlham Newsletter. See p.4, letter from EWT, 1972 (Box 185:, Folder 3655)
      - Earlham Newsletter. See p.9, 12, 18, 1973 (Box 185:, Folder 3656)
      - Everyday Reading. "King of the Grassroot Jungles", 11:8, 1943 January (Box 185:, Folder 3657)
      - Famous Writers Magazine. Green, John J. "Why Not Try Nature Stories?", 1967 Summer (Box 185:, Folder 3658)
      - Fauna. "Fiddler's Progress", 4:1, 1942 March (Box 185:, Folder 3659)
      - Fauna. "Insect Birthdays", 5:2, 1943 June (Box 185:, Folder 3660)
      - Fauna. "Insect Appetite Number One", 6:3, 1944 September (Box 185:, Folder 3661)
      - Fauna. "Mangrove Wilderness", 8:1, 1946 March (Box 185:, Folder 3662)
      - Fauna. "Insect Trapper", 8:3, 1946 September (Box 185:, Folder 3663)
      - Flower Grower. Teale, Nellie Donovan "New Iris Varieties-The Rainbow Children", 22:10, 1935 October (Box 185:, Folder 3664)
      - Flower Grower. "Victory Flowers", 29:10, 1942 October (Box 185:, Folder 3665)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 42:4, 1950, April (Box 185:, Folder 3666)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 42:5, 1950 May (Box 185:, Folder 3667)
      - Ford Times. "Nature Invented It First", 42:6, 1950 June (Box 185:, Folder 3668)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 42:7, 1950 July (Box 185:, Folder 3669)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 42:8, 1950 August (Box 185:, Folder 3670)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 42:9, 1950 September (Box 185:, Folder 3671)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 43:5, 1951 May (Box 185:, Folder 3672)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 43:6, 1951 June (Box 185:, Folder 3673)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 43:7, 1951 July (Box 185:, Folder 3674)
      - Ford Times. "What Is It?", 44:1, 1952 January (Box 185:, Folder 3675)
      - Ford Times. "Mountains in Flowers", 45:5, 1953 May (Box 185:, Folder 3676)
      - Frontiers. "Pinhead Portraits", 7:4, 1943 April (Box 185:, Folder 3677)
      - Garden Path. Lawson, Helen "The FBI of Your Garden", 19:3, 1949 April/June (Box 185:, Folder 3678)
      - Gleanings in Bee Culture. Photo p.548, 71:9, 1943 September (Box 185:, Folder 3679)
      - Gleanings in Bee Culture. Cover photo, 1950 June (Box 185:, Folder 3679B)
      - The Guide to Nature. "The Skunk Cabbage", 27:3, 1935 Spring (Box 185:, Folder 3680)
      - The Guide to Nature. "The Black Swallowtail", 27:4, 1935 Summer (Box 185:, Folder 3681)
      - The Hampton Gazette. Unknown article, 2:6 & 3:3, 1979 September, 1980 June (Box 186:, Folder 3682)
      - The Hampton Gazette. "Nellie is Ninety", 11:7, 1990 October (Box 186:, Folder 3683)
      - Heirlooms. "The Open World"- photocopy only, 1967 (Box 186:, Folder 3684)
      - Illinois Magazine. Wells, Catherine W. "Edwin Way Teale", 23:6, 1984 November/December (Box 186:, Folder 3685)
      - Insect Life. Boy Scouts Merit Badge Series, 1944 (Box 186:, Folder 3686)
      - Inklings. Whittle, Eric. S., "Springtime in Britain", 2:1, 1977 Autumn (Box 186:, Folder 3687)
      - Jack and Jill. Photo p.57, 10:8, 1948 June (Box 186:, Folder 3688)
      - Jack and Jill. Photo p.56, 58, 1948 November (Box 186:, Folder 3689)
      - The Joy of Spring. Quotes from EWT, 1948 November (Box 186:, Folder 3690)
      - Junior Natural History. "Pray for Your Supper", 4:7, 1939 September (Box 186:, Folder 3691)
      - Ladies Home Journal. Photocopies of articles., 1947 (Box 186:, Folder 3692)
      - Leiss. "Grassroot Jungles", 3:11, 1937 November (Box 186:, Folder 3693)
      - Liberty. Linn, Elizabeth "Why Bees Keep So Busy", 1945 June 23 (Box 186:, Folder 3694)
      - The Living Church. Cover Photo., 1960 July (Box 186:, Folder 3695)
      - Living Tissue. Photo p.7, 28:10, 1943 October (Box 186:, Folder 3696)
      - The Lone Scout. "Summer Time is Butterfly Time", 19:7, 1945 July (Box 186:, Folder 3697)
      - Magazine Digest. "Edwin Way Teale: Nature's Best Friend" copy of article only., 1949 January (Box 186:, Folder 3698)
      - Minicam. "Backyard Dinosaurs", 1:5, 1938 January (Box 186:, Folder 3699)
      - Minicam. "Insect Silhouettes", 6:11, 1943 July (Box 186:, Folder 3700)
      - Musecam. "Photographing Insects", 2:5, 1940 May (Box 186:, Folder 3701)
      - Natural History. "Knothole Cavern", 50:3, 1942 October (Box 187:, Folder 3702)
      - Natural History. "Where do Insects go in Winter?", 51:1, 1943 January (Box 187:, Folder 3703)
      - Natural History. "Hills that Walk", 52:2, 1943 September (Box 187:, Folder 3704)
      - Natural History. "Butterfly Botanist", 57:7, 1948 September (Box 187:, Folder 3705)
      - Natural History. "The Bird that Baffled a Continent", 59:4, 1950 April (Box 187:, Folder 3706)
      - Natural History. "How to Collect Seaweeds", 66:5, 1957 May (Box 187:, Folder 3707)
      - Natural History. "The Oldest Migration", 66:7, 1957 September (Box 187:, Folder 3708)
      - Natural History. " `Sleeping One' of the Hopis", 74:10, 1965 December (Box 187:, Folder 3709)
      - The Nature Conservancy News. "When a Project Becomes a Preserve", 19:1, 1969 Spring (Box 187:, Folder 3710)
      - The Nature Conservancy Newsletter. Unknown article., 1988 Summer (Box 187:, Folder 3711)
      - Nature in Action -bound book., 1946 January - November (Box 187:, Folder 3712)
      - Nature in Action articles., 1946 January - March (Box 187:, Folder 3713)
      - Nature in Action articles, 1946 April - August (Box 188:, Folder 3714)
      - Nature in Action articles, 1946 August - November (Box 188:, Folder 3715)
      - Nature Magazine. "The Poodle and the `Coon", 29:1, 1937 January (Box 188:, Folder 3716)
      - Nature Magazine. "Insect Mysteries", "Wing Windows", 35:7, 1942 August/September (Box 188:, Folder 3717)
      - Nature Magazine. "False Pussywillows", 35:10, 1942 December (Box 188:, Folder 3718)
      - Nature Magazine. "E. Laurence Palmer", 36:6, 1943 June/July (Box 188:, Folder 3719)
      - Nature Magazine. "Cherished by the Pioneers", 36:7, 1943 August/September (Box 188:, Folder 3720)
      - Nature Magazine. "Schoolyard Sanctuary", 37:2, 1944 February (Box 188:, Folder 3721)
      - Nature Magazine. Zahniser, Howard. "Nature in Print" proof, 1946 (Box 188:, Folder 3722)
      - Nature Magazine. "Sleeping Beauties of the Winter Wood", 37:3, 1944 March (Box 189:, Folder 3723)
      - Nature Magazine. "Lucky Bugs, and Others", 37:7, 1944 August/September (Box 189:, Folder 3724)
      - Nature Magazine. "DDT", 38:3, 1945 March (Box 189:, Folder 3725)
      - Nature Magazine. "The World's Most Useful Legs", 38:5, 1945 May (Box 189:, Folder 3726)
      - Nature Magazine. "A Clump of Grass", 41:6, 1948 June/July (Box 189:, Folder 3727)
      - Nature Magazine. "Tail Tales", 41:7, 1948 August/September (Box 189:, Folder 3728)
      - Nature Magazine. Zahniser, Howard "Nature in Print", 49:5, 1956 May (Box 189:, Folder 3729)
      - Nature Magazine. "Patches", 51:8, 1958 October (Box 189:, Folder 3730)
      - Nature Magazine. "Natural History Changes", 52:3, 1959 March (Box 189:, Folder 3731)
      - 3915 NCLA Odds and Book Ends. "Radio Series Promotes Books of L.I. Authors" no.8, 1950 Autumn (Box 189:, Folder 3731B)
      - NCLA Odds and Book Ends. Cover Photo, no.11, 1952 Spring (Box 189:, Folder 3732)
      - New England Wild Flower Notes. "The Pasture Rose", 1975 Fall (Box 189:, Folder 3733)
      - New York National Guardsman. "Harry Pope's Rifle Barrels", 13:4, 1936 July (Box 189:, Folder 3734)
      - Newsweek. "The World of a Bee" review of The Golden Throng, 1940 November 11 (Box 189:, Folder 3735)
      - Outdoor Life. "He Makes the Finest Rifle Barrels...", 74:5, 1934 November (Box 189:, Folder 3736)
      - Outdoor Life. "Fitz: Two-Gun Speed Merchant", 75:2, 1935 February (Box 189:, Folder 3737)
      - Outdoor Life. "Footprint Hunter" photocopy of article only, 1935 September (Box 189:, Folder 3738)
      - Outdoor Life. "Father of the Six Gun", 77:1, 1936 January (Box 189:, Folder 3739)
      - Outdoor Life. "Your Gun...", 90:3, 1942 September (Box 189:, Folder 3740)
      - Outdoor Life. "Handgun's Family Album", 91:2, 1943 February (Box 189:, Folder 3741)
      - Outdoor Life. "Wonder Stove From Old Tin Cans", 91:3, 1943 March (Box 189:, Folder 3742)
      - Outdoor Life. "Woodcraft Goes to War", 91:4, 1943 April (Box 189:, Folder 3743)
      - Outdoor Life. Article Unknown, 91:5, 1943 May (Box 189:, Folder 3744)
      - Outdoor Life. "Science Makes Fish Fight- With Vitamins", 91:6, 1943 June (Box 189:, Folder 3745)
      - Outdoor Life. "A Pack Sack From A Pair of Pants", 92:2, 1943 August (Box 190:, Folder 3746)
      - Outdoor Life. "Ideas that Made Rifle History", 92:5, 1943 November (Box 190:, Folder 3747)
      - Outdoor Life. Article Unknown, 92:6, 1943 December (Box 190:, Folder 3748)
      - Outdoor Life. "Pheasant Factory" photocopy of article, 1942 October (Box 190:, Folder 3749)
      - Outdoor Life. "His Eyes Are Everywhere" photocopy of article, 1943 January (Box 190:, Folder 3750)
      - Outdoor Life. "Flintock to Garland", 93:3, 1944 March (Box 190:, Folder 3751)
      - Outdoor Life. "Your Hunting Knife Has a History", 94:4, 1944 October (Box 190:, Folder 3752)
      - Outdoor Life. Article Unknown, 105:6, 1950 June (Box 190:, Folder 3753)
      - Outdoor Life. "Rattlers Are His Game", 106:6, 1950 December (Box 190:, Folder 3754)
      - PB Pocket Book Magazine. "Those Phenomenal Insects", no.2, 1955 February (Box 190:, Folder 3755)
      - Pennsylvania Angler. "The Strength of the Cattail", 21:3, 1952 March (Box 190:, Folder 3756)
      - People Places and Things. "Creatures of the Summer Garden", 1960 (Box 190:, Folder 3757)
      - Photo Magazine. "Pets Buy My Film for Me", 1:1, 1936 September (Box 190:, Folder 3758)
      - Popular Science Articles. Photocopies only., 1930-1932 (Box 190:, Folder 3759)
      - Popular Science Articles. Photocopies only., 1933-1936 (Box 190:, Folder 3760)
      - Popular Science Articles- bound book, 1938-1941 (Box 190:, Folder 3761)
      - Punch. "David Williams: On Hearing the First Botanist of Spring", 1971 March (Box 190:, Folder 3762)
      - Reader's Digest. "Flying With a Test Pilot", 18:103, 1930 November (Box 190:, Folder 3763)
      - Reader's Digest. "Radio Snares for Crooks", 18:104, 1930 December (Box 190:, Folder 3764)
      - Reader's Digest. "Black Light' Traps Crooks", 19:114, 1931 October (Box 190:, Folder 3765)
      - Reader's Digest Articles- photocopies only, 1933-1935 (Box 191:, Folder 3766)
      - Reader's Digest. Section of Dune Boy, 1944 May (Box 191:, Folder 3767)
      - Reader's Digest. Section of Dune Boy, 44:266, 1944 June (Box 191:, Folder 3768)
      - Reader's Digest. "Chico de las dunas" section of Dune Boy, 16:9, 1944 September (Box 191:, Folder 3769)
      - Reader's Digest. "Be a Back-Yard Explorer", 1952 August (Box 191:, Folder 3770)
      - Reader's Digest. "Be a Back-Yard Explorer", different edition, 1952 August (Box 191:, Folder 3771)
      - Reader's Digest. "Be a Back-Yard Explorer", different edition, 1952 September (Box 191:, Folder 3772)
      - Reader's Digest. "Be a Back-Yard Explorer", Brittish? edition, 1952 September (Box 191:, Folder 3773)
      - Reader's Digest. "Explore el huerto de su casa", Spanish edition, 1952 November (Box 192:, Folder 3774)
      - Reader's Digest. "The Walks of Winter", 1979 March (Box 192:, Folder 3775)
      - Reader's Digest. "A Journey Through July", 1980 July (Box 192:, Folder 3776)
      - Reader's Digest. "November's Magic", 1980 November (Box 192:, Folder 3777)
      - Reader's Digest. "Quotable Quotes", some by EWT, 1980 December (Box 192:, Folder 3778)
      - Reader's News. "Adventures in an Insect Garden" 12:3, 1949 August; (2 copies), (Box 192:, Folder 3779)
      - Reader's Digest. Advertisement mentions EWT, 12:4, 1949 September (Box 192:, Folder 3780)
      - Recreation. "A Schoolyard Sanctuary", 38:12, 1945 March (Box 192:, Folder 3781)
      - The Saturday Review of Literature. "W. H. Hudson's Lost Years" By EWT & Gordon Wasson, 30:15, 1947 April 12 (Box 192:, Folder 3781B)
      - School Nature League Bulletin. 12:9, 18:1, 1942/1947 (Box 192:, Folder 3782)
      - School Nature League Bulletin. Order Form- photo by EWT, 1947 June (Box 192:, Folder 3782B)
      - Science Digest. "Tricks of Animal Schoolteachers", 19:2, 1946 February (Box 192:, Folder 3783)
      - Scientific American. "The Language of the Bees", lists EWT as source, 179:2, 1948 August (Box 192:, Folder 3784)
      - SRA Reading Laboratory Teacher's Handbook., 1958 (Box 192:, Folder 3785)
      - Success Today. Weston, Charles Henry "Teale Exposed Himself to Good Fortune" article only, 1947/1948 Winter (Box 192:, Folder 3785B)
      - Traces. Weber, Catherine E. Forrest. "Always the Other Spring!: The Life and Nature Writing of Edwin Way Teale", 7:2, 1995 Spring (Box 192:, Folder 3786)
      - "Trail Wood, Hampton, Connecticut: Vegetation of the Edwin Way Teale Memorial Sanctuary" Egler, Frank E., 1987 (Box 192:, Folder 3786B)
      - University of Connecticut Newsletters., 1987 Spring-Fall (Box 192:, Folder 3787)
      - U.S. Camera. "Close-up on Insects", 13:4, 1950 April (Box 192:, Folder 3788)
      - Watch the Birds, Photo by EWT, 1951 (Box 192:, Folder 3789)
      - "Way Teale's Daily Editorial" original proofs, 1928 (Box 192:, Folder 3790)
      - Yankee. Chadwick, Paul. "The Golden Hours of Edwin Way Teale", 28:5, 1964 May (Box 192:, Folder 3791)
      - Ye Anglican. "Firelight Faces", 1:2, 1922 June (Box 192:, Folder 3792)
      - Yearbook Separate of Agriculture. "Oddities of the Insect World", 1952 (Box 192:, Folder 3793)
      - Your Life. "Strengthen Your Muscles of Decision", 41:3, 1960 July (Box 192:, Folder 3794)
      - Zoo Life. Photo by EWT p. 145, 9:4, 1954 Winter (Box 192:, Folder 3795)
      - Unknown Magazine. Graham, Frank Jr. "The Last Naturalist" (Article only), undated (Box 192:, Folder 3795B)
  - Subseries B: Printed Material not containing EWT, undated, 1885-1984
    - Adams Features Magazine., 1925 September (Box 193:, Folder 3796)
    - Additional Observations on the Sleep of Insects Rau, Phil, undated (Box 193:, Folder 3797)
    - Audubon., 51:5, 1949 September/October (Box 193:, Folder 3798)
    - Aero Digest. Unknown article., 1932 May (Box 193:, Folder 3799)
    - The American City. (pp.69-70 missing), 48:10, 1933 October (Box 193:, Folder 3800)
    - American Ornithology. 5:1, 1901 May (Box 193:, Folder 3801)
    - Animal Kingdom. Article Unknown, 47:6, 1944 November/December (Box 193:, Folder 3802)
    - Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences. Breder, C.M. & Edgerton, H. "An Analysis of the Locomotion of the..." v.43, 1942 June (Box 193:, Folder 3803)
    - Appalachia. Woodworth, John. "A Song for the Sora", 1967 December (Box 193:, Folder 3804)
    - Auditory Perception in Insects, Rau, Phil, 1940 June (Box 193:, Folder 3805)
    - "Audubon and Wilson..." Stringham, Emerson. Reprint, 1953 Winter (Box 193:, Folder 3806)
    - The Auk. Stoner, Dayton. "American Egret Along the Upper Hudson River" reprint v.55, 1938 January (Box 193:, Folder 3807)
    - The Auk. Stoner, Dayton. "Noteworthy Records for Northeastern New York" v.57, 1940 July (Box 193:, Folder 3808)
    - The Auk. Stoner, Dayton. "A Noteworthy Concentration of Birds", 1941 October (Box 193:, Folder 3809)
    - The Auk. Stoner, Dayton. "Longevity and Other Data on a Captive English Sparrow" v.59, 1942 July (Box 193:, Folder 3810)
    - "Avian Migration at Rancho Grande in North-Central Venezuela" Beebe, W., 1949 June 3 (Box 193:, Folder 3811)
    - Back to Nature, Cummin, Mel. Autographed & dedicated, 1945 (Box 193:, Folder 3812)
    - Bartholomew's Cobble, Bailey & Arnold, undated (Box 193:, Folder 3813)
    - Bird Banding. Stoner, Dayton. "Behavior of Young Bank...", 13:3, 1942 July (Box 193:, Folder 3814)
    - Bird Casualties at..., Stoddard, Herbert, 1962 (Box 193:, Folder 3815)
    - Bird Life of Canada's Niagara Frontier, Sheppard, R.W. Signed and noted by author, 1960 October 22 (Box 193:, Folder 3816)
    - Bird Life of Virginia, Shoman, Joseph, 1951 (Box 193:, Folder 3817)
    - Birds of Long Island, Nichols, J.T., 1948 January (Box 193:, Folder 3818)
    - Botanical Museum Leaflets. Wasson, Gordon. "Hallucinogenic Mushrooms Of Mexico..." 20:2, 1962 September 7 (Box 193:, Folder 3819)
    - The Bulletin. Unknown article. No.70, 1955 Fall (Box 193:, Folder 3820)
    - The Bulletin. Unknown article. No.80, 1958 June (Box 193:, Folder 3821)
    - Bulletin of the American Museum of Natural History. Raven, H.C., 1939 September 8 (Box 193:, Folder 3822)
    - Bulletin of the Southern California Academy of Sciences. Brach, Vincent. "The Biology of the Social Spider", 74:1, 1975 April (Box 194:, Folder 3823)
    - "Butterflies of New Jersey" Comstock, William P. v.48, 1940 March (Box 194:, Folder 3824)
    - California Garden. Lippitt, Marion A. "Leaves from the Observer's Notebook", 45:2, 1954 Summer (Box 194:, Folder 3825)
    - The Camp Fire Girl. Unknown article., 1952 Apr/May/June (Box 194:, Folder 3826)
    - Changes in the Natural History..., Mayfield, Howard, 1962 June (Box 194:, Folder 3827)
    - Chronica Botanica. Rafineque, C.S. "A Life of Travels", 8:2, 1944 Spring (Box 194:, Folder 3828)
    - The Condor. Unknown Article, 30:1, 1928 January/February (Box 194:, Folder 3829)
    - Conservation of Plants & Conservation of Water, St. of Indiana, 1945, 1946 (Box 194:, Folder 3830)
    - Conservation Sketchbook, Schwartz, C.W., 1950 (Box 194:, Folder 3831)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Woody Plants in America", 15:2, 1921 November (Box 194:, Folder 3832)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Amphibia & Reptilia", 15:4, 1922 March (Box 194:, Folder 3833)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Spring Flowers", 16:4, 1923 March (Box 194:, Folder 3834)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Larger Mammals", 19:2, 1925 November (Box 194:, Folder 3835)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Fungi", 21:2, 1927 November (Box 194:, Folder 3836)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet. "Flowers of Woody Plants", 23:4, 1930 March (Box 194:, Folder 3837)